<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Aela Wild</title>
    <link>https://latimerae.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Aela Wild</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://latimerae.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beans</title>
      <link>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-10-02-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-10-02-beans/</guid>
      <description>Here’s my entry for the Noxon Challenge proposed by Edu Puertas on youtube! The challenge was to create a 10 second short with camera movement. The prize is a noxon slider. Of course a slider would change the way I work and improve my process, but I loved the idea of the challenge. I only had a five days to make it, and I’m really happy with how it turned out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making of Stars of Stone</title>
      <link>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-09-20-sosmakingof/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-09-20-sosmakingof/</guid>
      <description>Now that the short is done I can finally share the years of footage and photos documenting the making-of process. I’m getting those into video format for YouTube, so expect a few short videos on the puppets, sets, and deleted scenes.
Watch this space!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stars of Stone</title>
      <link>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-09-05-stars-of-stone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-09-05-stars-of-stone/</guid>
      <description>Great news, Rook’s first adventure is complete. It’s currently doing the rounds of some film festivals, so I can’t share it publicly or it would be disqualified. Thankfully my lovely Patreon supporters get early access now because donors are allowed to see it early!
Here’s a little teaser.
  I would love to know what you think!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop-Mo Jam 2021</title>
      <link>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-09-19-stopmojamhalloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-09-19-stopmojamhalloween/</guid>
      <description>This year’s Stop-Mo Jam, hosted over at Stop Motion Animation, had a Halloween theme!
That’s my jam.I’ve been working hard to limit my projects, so I finished Stars of Stone first, in the last days of August. And then right away I rolled into prop-making for this one.
First, six or seven thin layers of paper strips in PVA glue on a baloon, then a layer of soaked and shredded egg cartons with PVA, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birds as Insulation (Draughts)</title>
      <link>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-3-20-birddoorstop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2021-3-20-birddoorstop/</guid>
      <description>It’s winter here in Australia and our front door has a weird doorstop and a huge gap below the door, so I designed a weirdo bird to fit under it. I originally wanted it to be a bittern and was planning on painting it, but I couldn’t bring myself to change it from egret form.
Then, after I made it, I used a thermal camera to have a look and see if it made a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Need Critter Graphics?</title>
      <link>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2020-11-07-animalscommission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2020-11-07-animalscommission/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made graphics for a few researchers at this point, so I was happy when my partner Timothee Bonnet needed some animal graphics for his projects. I was happy to oblige and they turned out pretty cute.
If you’d like something similar for a project of yours, get in touch and we can discuss pricing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toothless Bear gets Teeth</title>
      <link>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2019-10-07-rsbear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://latimerae.github.io/post/2019-10-07-rsbear/</guid>
      <description>This American black bear (Ursus americanus) was donated to the ANU to raise awareness of illegal trafficking and animal imports. Along the way, the bear lost her original fishy mouthful was feeling a bit toothless. The Ecology and Evolution group at the Australian National University tasked me with fitting her for prosthesis and doing a touch-up. This included cleaning the mouth and preparing it for new teeth, 3D printing some teeth from a CT scan, editing them down to fit the bear’s age, sculpting a new palate seating and painting it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
